# Hisham Harmalanee

UAE • +971 58 5952081

Eng.hishamharmalanee@gmail.com linkedIn.com/in/hishamharmalanee/ mostaql.com/u/Hisham\_Ha/portfolio

# **Business Developer**

Business Developer with +5 years of experience in marketing. Content writing, analyzing SEO, and managing content. Experienced in marketing, feasibility study, project management, sales planning, and networking. Interested in identifying new business opportunities, developing and implementing strategies to increase revenue, and building relationships with potential clients and partners.

## **Areas of Expertise**

- Feasibility Study
- Business Model

Business Plan

Marketing

Networking

• Business Strategy

- Project Management
- Target Audience

Communication

## Achievement

- Incubated as the top ten entrepreneurial projects in the Entrepreneurship Center of the Damascus Chamber of Commerce
- Ranked as the fastest freelancer who has a trusted seller grade -The highest grade on the Khamsat platform- within 6 months
- Sold +225 services on the Khamsat platform for 50 clients with 5 stars rate.
- Achieved +50 projects on the Mostaql platform with 5 stars rate.

## **Career Experience**

Marketing Specialist, Alholem Almotamyez, Abu Dhabi

01/2023 - Present

- Developing +10 marketing plans that outline strategies for promoting brands, products, or services.
- Managing all campaigns and tracking their success through metrics such as conversions and engagement rates of more than 75% of successful campaigns.
- Analyzing +300 data tables to gain insights into customer behavior, identifying areas for improvement, and adjusting campaigns as needed.
- Collaborating with +3 cross-functional teams such as sales, product development, and customer service, to align marketing efforts with business goals.
- Monitoring the project teams ensuring +20 contracts are executed as agreed.

Freelancer 04/2021 – Present

#### Content Writer:

- Creating content for +50 clients on Mostaql and Khamsat platforms till now. https://khamsat.com/user/hisham\_h86/reviews
- Created +25 articles for Mostaql and Baaeed till May 2022.
   https://blog.mostaql.com/author/hesham-harmelany/

#### SEO Analyzer:

- Analyzing +50 sites to detect the errors and warnings that affect website rankings.
- Supervising the repair of +10000 errors and checking results.
- Creating +10 SEO plans that support rank improvement.

### Content Manager, Eradd for Accounting consultancy

 Created +25 articles for the company blog till December 2022. https://eradapp.com/blog/

...continued...

- Supervised the executive leadership of a team of 4 employees.
- Met with +200 sales-qualified leads and got to know their needs.
- Participated with the marketing team to develop +20 market plans.
- Solved IT issues in Pre-Sales, with a 90% quality-to-cost ratio.
- Developed mutually beneficial proposals by coordinating with the sales team of 5 people.
- Provided high-level technical training to +200 end-users on customer premises to build a first level of support.
- Coordinated +100 activities to deploy a complete IT solution and ensure compliance with signed agreements and managed +10 strategic partnerships to grow business.

#### **CCIT Learning Center**

Member of Management Board

10/2014 - 08/2022

- Created +300 presentations to prospective B2B clients to help them with their choices.
- Created and implemented +50 processes and policies to support the overall business.

IT Trainer 10/2012 - 12/2022

- Dealt with problems that appeared during the training (+50 courses).
- Trained +500 trainees on MS Excel for advanced levels, CCNA 200-125, and 200-301 Courses, Microsoft courses such as MCSE 2012 and MCITP, CompTIA courses such as "Network+" and Computer Maintenance "A+", ICDL v6 Courses.

	— Additional Experience ———	
IT Supervisor, E-Payment Company, Damascus		05/2018 - 04/2020
Project Coordinator, ICC with Kantel, Damascus		07/2017 - 04/2018
Trainer, New Horizons, Damascus		09/2015 - 07/2017
Network Administrator, Industrial Bank, Damascus		09/2011 - 04/2015
	— Courses ————	
	Marketing	
• 3x1 MBA Marketing Diploma	Market Research	• Digital Marketing Business
<ul> <li>Introduction to Social Media Marketing</li> </ul>	• SEO training to TOP rank your website	• TikTok Marketing
	Sales	
• Sales and CRM	• Lead Management in Salesforce	• Opportunity Management in
• System Sales Funnels		Salesforce
	Management	
• PMP 35 PDU	• Feasibility Study	• HR Management
Business Model Canvas	• Contracts	• Customer Care

#### Education

#### Master Of Business Administration MBA

Syrian Virtual University, Damascus, Syria - Online

#### Bachelor Of Engineering in Electron and Communication

Damascus University, Damascus, Syria